# SURASAK THEERATHONGDEE

Programmer

## **PROFILE**

I had to work for a part-time job while I was studying. I worked at Paper lunch and Swensens after I finished the class. All of my free time was spent on my part-time job. Then, I joined an internship. I learning programming and develop program with python language, so the company hired me in part time job in programmer position after finished the internship program. I graduated with an Electrical Engineering degree but I like programming so I need to work as a programmer.



80/854 Bangkaew, Bangphe, Samutprakan 10540

surasak.theerathongdee@gmail.com



https://srskmai.github.io/Portfolio



08-8942-9491



## **EDUCATION**

Bachelor Degree in Electrical Engineering Kasetsart University, 2016 Bangkok, Thailand

Hign School Saithammachan school, 2010 Ratchaburi, Thailand

# **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS, PHP

**Codeigniter Framework** 

Javascript (Ajax, Jquery)

vb (Window application)

ASP.Net

# DATABASE

Mysql

Postgresql

SQLserver

## **EXPERIENCE**

### PROGRAMMER

- develop ERP system with codeigniter and MySQL
- develop web application with codeigniter and MySQL

### SYSTEM DESIGN ENGINEERING

- Develop webapplication for engineering section wiht php and PostgreSQL
- Modify window appliucation (Program KANBAN) with VB and SQL Server
- Training ASP.Net in 9Expert Corporation

#### PROGRAMMER

- (Worked past time and full time)
- Develop web application with Yii2 Framwork and PostgreSQL
- Develop mobile application with Ionic Framwork
- Develop flash game with Action Script

### PART TIME

- Swensens
- Papper lunch

DELTA NETWORK SOLUTION BANGKOK 2019-PRESENT

DAICEL SAFETY SYSTEM
PRACHINBURI
2017-2018

CHULABHON SATELLITE RECEIVING STATION
BANGKOK
2013-2016

BANGKOK

2011-2013